Warning: TH1s document expla1ns Every single event that occurs throughout the entire t1meline. It is a file to be regarded with the greatest of cautioN and only to be revealed when the Time is ripe. OncE they are able to solve the iNterconnected web seen within the ____ , it will all piece together to create what he is looking for.
[Opening...]
LeonarDo was a young boy born into the relatively Small suburb of Mill Park. He grew up living a Tough life, considering that bOth his parents had started neglecting him at the ripe age of ten. They had given birth to him young, which meant that they did not really Feel ready to take care of the chIld and only kept him arouNd due to obligation.

[Background inf0 Complete]

[Processing…]

The campIng trip. It was where everything waS intertwined. It was wHere everything that he had planned fit into place. Leonardo began his minor infatuation with [____] when he was young, and that only grew stronger as he matured. EventuallY, it turned intO hatred, as another competitor entered the fray. 

So he instituted his plan early. Joy, her best friend happened to be collateral. With another boy called Nelson, he managed to call in a trip to New York due to pure lUck, and set out his ideas in motion. It was soon set up, and under a clever pretence, they all headed out for a ‘luxury vacation’. 

There, the deed was done. [Ending 10]. [Decoding....] [Message found: Open?]

[DECLINED]

Now all of this might seem irrelevant. But afterwards, through a deal struck with a certain tech company, Leonardo was able to shroud himself under a veil of safety even while his friend James took the fall. Her squabbling parents had no clue upon the matter, too focused upon what caused this to strike back.

But a broken-hearted friend took their case up with Anonymous, who knew the truth behind the shady deals within the company.

Corruption. Brokenness. Chaos, chaos.

Anthony Schmidt took up the deal, along with a few others. And they began their attack.

This leak was soon spread throughout the company as the emails started to flood in. Of course, the higher ups were alerted immediately, and you were sent to investigate. In the end, the company’s wealth allowed them to strike first, and they were soon given access to hashes also given to you to decrypt.

Now you will hand them all the answers. Alex Spolsky, the founder of MYRIAD will bring his full hand upon you. Within a matter of days, your next challenge will begin.

It will not end here, for those who trek this path. There are secrets within secrets, lies within lies, this is just a glimpse of truth within the hardened world.

But first there is one mor .-.. .. ... - . -. / - --- / -- . --..-- / .... .. ... / .-- --- .-. -.. ... / .- .-. . / .-.. .. . ... / ... .--. .-. .. -. .-.. . -.. / .. -. / - .-. ..- - .... .-.-.- / -... ..- - / - .... . / -- --- ... - / .. -- .--. --- .-. - .- -. - / .-- --- .-. -.. ... / .- .-. . / .-. .. --. .... - .-.-.- / .... . / .. ... / - .-. --- ..- -... .-.. . .-.-.- / .... . / .... .- ... / --. --- -. . / ..- -. -.. . .-. / -- .- -. -.-- / -. .- -- . ... --..-- / .-.. . --- -. .- .-. -.. --- / -.- .- .--. .--. --..-- / .- .-.. . -..- / ... .--. --- .-.. ... -.- -.-- --..-- / -.- -.-. .... .-.. --- . --..-- / -... ..- - / - .... .-. --- ..- --. .... / .. - / .- .-.. .-.. --..-- / .... .. ... / .-.. .- ... - / .-- .. ... .... / .-- .- ... / - .... .- - / .... . / .-- .- ... / -. --- - / -.. .. ... -.-. --- ...- . .-. . -.. .-.-.- / .... . / .-- .. .-.. .-.. / --. --- / .- ..-. - . .-. / -.-- --- ..- .-.-.- / .... . / .-- .. .-.. .-.. / -. --- - / .-. . ... - / ..- -. - .. .-.. / .... .. ... / .. -.. . -. - .. - -.-- / .. ... / .--. .-. . ... . .-. ...- . -.. .-.-.- / -.-- --- ..- / -- ..- ... - ..- .--. .--. -- -... ..- ..-. ..- .--. .--. -- -... ..- ..-. / ..- .--. .--. -- -... ..- ..-. / ..- .--. .--. -- -... ..- ..-. / ..- .--. .--. -- -... ..- ..-. / ..- .--. .--. -- -... ..- ..-. / ..- .--. .--. -- -... ..- ..-. / ..- .--. .--. -- -... ..- ..-. / 

[Recording ended]

[Processing… Open File her.ogg?]

[DECLINED.]

[Closing…]
